I have to tell of odd that the eclipse are ready to strike.
After what happened with Durval.
I know I'll defend the city
with the spire
just wrapped inspection of guy a prime site.
Construction is well underway.
Reactor installed Plans for control room remind me of Starship Bridges on those cheesy old SF bids.
Living spaces were office already completed.
Prefab modules, fingers crossed.
We never have to seal ourselves in here.
Now that Elysium sounds much better spent last week at the Bryce site, designing said T Project Lab's Drawing Up Protocols Base, where repurposing was huge, plenty of room for work spaces and residents blocks work crews already set up my office.
I'm not a fan of the glass wall guest.
Murray's intention was doing Sconce Me is all seeing presence.
Uh, opposite effect makes me feel watched on display.
Tempted to paint it over, Harris recorded his presentation yesterday suitably bleak.
Scheduled to record line Friday.
Assume this reception Lounge Hollow Theatres and First Residents block.
It's a decider.
Finished.
We'll start processing the candidates being held outside Tucson, 27 already extraction teams prioritising pack room and Aussie candidates.
How scared and confused they must be snatched off the street, carted across the world health and sounds.
Here's hoping they understand once they see the big picture going to catch a few hours, sleep here, then fly back to the set D site.
Harris promised delivery of Cuban lattices by noon.
Expect Mark.
One will take two weeks to machine.
Assemble and test.
I aim to launch guy at 20.60 Grounding From there, I'll spend her up past 20.
Wonder how long it'll take to break the 1.3 80 record and I can go Hang.
Sleep
quickly down.
You
all right?
Who?
No,
these trails.
Okay?
Drawing back.
Maybe you maybe.
What are you doing?
I can still get the upper hand.
Stay down!
Keep quiet Now
Maybe I've spent too much time with you.
I can almost feel the lightning in this.
On the taste metal striking sparks along a sharpening stone.
Lingering here, Touch it to your tongue and know that's your thing, not mine.
You look startled.
Are you okay?
I
I must leave You should too.
Is that a storey?
I brought down a storm bird.
You did your very able And you're right Old is old but no more storeys of the past.
All told all done
future storeys
I saw on a GN rushing storm
The future comes hungry for man on machine
It will catch me I expect catch a soul So enough hunts enough visions I'll run Chase that teasing son to the forbidden West I I don't understand.
I mean, now that I ever understand But are you saying we should fear what's coming?
Oh, yes.
Jungle on fire Machine blue light dying out in the Eddies of ashes You fallen pale as snow Flash eyes staring open
the metal world But not the one I sought
The future is a frightful dream Huntress, My name is a lawyer.
I grew fond of you,
your curiosity's and disbelief ce a lot.
If you weather this storm,
look for me.
I like that.
Where?
In the west?
In the store.
In dreams?
Yes.
Go
machines.
Really?
Thank you.
Stocking up.
Okay.
Come.
Go!
Catch up.
Fascinating.
Working for me.
The clamps have the armour locked in place.
Maybe there's a way to power the mechanism.
Release clamps
Only two more.
Just one more.
There we go.
The last one
all powered up.
Now to get the dials and physician, you must be case numbers.
They must be related to segments of a circle.
Let's have a look at that armour inside.
All right, Now let's see what we can do with this material.
Ultra Leave Mark 71 Trials October 65 Trial 49 b October 3rd 2065 Past threshold 85 of 100 results.
Ballistic Test 91 Shrapnel Test 87 Laser Test 88 Shield Integrity 86 Impact Tour So 51 armed 62 legs 43 Notes.
We've is not tightening properly on local impact tests.
We need to optimise existing sensors.
Read more trying 51 K.
October 5th 2065 Past threshold 85 of 100 Results Ballistic Test 88 Shrapnel Test 91 Laser Test 87 Shield Integrity 87 Impact Tour So 67 armed 75 legs.
81 notes Sensor optimisation successful but torso protection still lacking.
Recommend increasing leave density trying 53 are October 6 2065 Past threshold 85 of 100 results Ballistic Test 92 Shrapnel Test 95 Laser Test 86 Shield Integrity 89.
Impact torso.
80 for arms, 81 legs.
13 notes getting there on the wave density and detection components.
But an integration error on the left knee tanked.
The impact test
subject isn't going to be able to walk that one off.
Surgery required.
Yeah.
Okay,
good.
You
I lost.
A lot has happened so high
I went inside the mountain.
Do you remember the night before the proving
the final lesson you taught me?
You said I need to disturb a purpose
bigger than myself.
Well hit
couldn't get much bigger.
It's the same purpose,
Dr.
Elizabeth gotcha.
When they were willing to die for So yeah,
we'll do it.
I give myself to that for Elizabeth Guy and for you.
I've got what I need to destroy Haiti's
The master over right now.
Will I have to do is drive it into Haiti skull.
So no problem there.
The final battle will be fought at Meridian.
Haiti's will come for the spire and I'll be ready.
I found out how Elizabeth died.
She sacrificed herself
as you might expect.
Said something about
going home.
I wonder where that was for her.
If I ever find out
I like to go there.
So you myself, assuming I actually survived the battle at Meridian, Of course, which, let's face it is well,
who knows?
Well, I
try to come back if I can, but
I I guess this
this might be it.
Thank you.
Crossed.
Thank you for everything.
You
No
great.